Bite my tongue bide my time
咬紧舌头沉默 等待我的机会
Wearing a warning sign
危险警告是我的保护色
Wait till the world is mine
等待 直到世界属于我的那一天到来
Visions I vandalize
肆意破坏美好的幻象
Cold in my kingdom size
在我的国土上寒风凛冽
Fell for these ocean eyes
沉醉于那一双海洋般的双眸
You should see me in a crown
你应该看到我头戴皇冠的模样
I'm gonna run this nothing town
我将要统治这个破落小镇
Watch me make 'em bow
看我是如何让他们对我俯首称臣
One by one by one
一个接一个接一个
One by one by
一个接一个
You should see me in a crown
你应该看到我头戴皇冠的模样
Your silence is my favorite sound
你的沉默是我最爱的声响
Watch me make 'em bow
看我是如何让他们对我俯首称臣
One by one by one
一个接一个接一个
Count my cards watch them fall
等着我的发牌 看他们一个个倒下
Blood on a marble wall
血染在大理石墙壁上
I like the way they all
我喜欢他们都
Scream
尖叫的模样
Tell me which one is worse
告诉我哪个才算更坏
Living or dying first
是苟延残喘还是了结此生
Sleeping inside a hearse
睡在棺材
I don't dream
我没有梦可做
You say
你说
Come over baby
来我身边吧亲爱的
I think you're pretty
我觉得你很漂亮
I'm okay
我也很好
I'm not your baby
我不是你的乖乖女
If you think I'm pretty
你也觉得我很漂亮
You should see me in a crown
你应该看到我头戴皇冠的模样
I'm gonna run this nothing town
我将要统治这个破落小镇
Watch me make 'em bow
看我是如何让他们对我俯首称臣
One by one by one
一个接一个接一个
One by one by
一个接一个
You should see me in a crown
你应该看到我头戴皇冠的模样
Your silence is my favorite sound
你的沉默是我最爱的声响
Watch me make 'em bow
看我是如何让他们对我俯首称臣
One by one by one
一个接一个接一个
Crown
皇冠
I'm gonna run this nothing town
我将要统治这个破落小镇
Watch me make 'em bow
看我是如何让他们对我俯首称臣
One by one by one
一个接一个接一个
You should see me in a crown
你应该看到我头戴皇冠的模样
Your silence is my favorite sound
你的沉默是我最爱的声响
Watch me make 'em bow
看我是如何让他们对我俯首称臣
One by one by one
一个接一个接一个